João Vítor Junckes

BEGINNER

CAREER OBJECTIVE

My name is Joao, I have 22 years old, I worked on SulAmerica and in BluVistoria, two companies mainly focus with automobile works. Nowdays I took the decision to turn things upside down and work with software and programming, something that I always had a love for it but never came across to learn.

I started learning pyhton, as I was recommend by friends, and now I'm learning HMTL, CSS and JavaScript.

HOW TO REACH ME:

Home: 89032138 Cell: 55 (47) 984855314 joaoljunckes@gmail.com 123 Fernandes Marques Brinhosa Street, Blumenau City, State of Santa Catarina, Brazil LinkedIn: @junckes Github:@Hhotre

WORK EXPERIENCE

Young Learner

SulAmerica| From July 2019 to Setember 2020

- I worked in a half-time job as a Young learner in SulAmerica Insurance of Automobiles
- Helped my team mates on their day to day job and customer service

Automobile Inspection

BluVistoria | Jun 2021 to August 2021

- Follow a list of steps to ensure that the car was following the laws of traffic in Brazil -Customer Service

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Adaptability to new environments
- Facility to work in team
- Dynamic and organized

EDUCATIONAL TRAINING

SENAI Institute

Automotive Mechanics Technician Course

- Attended Sept. 2017 to June 2018

Adolpho Konder High School

High School Complete

- Attended Sept. 2009 to June 2013